If this is really Fang Qingcheng,
I'm afraid Xin'er will never come back.
Young Master.
We guessed right.
What do we do now?
Put on a full show.
After all, Qingcheng
must stay alive to attend the Makeup Selection Ceremony.
Zi'er,
go find Fang Zhuozhuo again.
Yes.
Cousin.
I didn't expect that when we parted that day,
it would be forever.
No.
This is not my cousin.
Not Fang Qingcheng?
I have bathed my cousin before.
She doesn't have a birthmark there.
Then why
is she wearing Fang Qingcheng's clothes?
My cousin's dress
is this year's new style.
Yunjin Pavilion
made no less than a hundred of them.
Find some people
to bury this girl.
Do you really think, Young Master,
that it was a trap set by Lady Fang?
We carried out the rescue of Xin'er
flawlessly.
The only people who entered the secret room,
besides you and me,
were her.
But what if Lady Fang
tells Fang Qingcheng about your intention to kill?
That's exactly what I want.
If she goes to find Fang Qingcheng,
it saves us the trouble of looking for her.
Find a few reliable people
to keep an eye on her whereabouts
and see if she leaves the manor.
When the moon is full, old friends return.
The Mid-Autumn Festival is approaching.
Watered with unrooted water at Yin hour every day,
and steamed and dried the gold powder soil three times.
I followed all the steps Chu Shengyi mentioned.
It's been a few days.
Strange.
Why hasn't it sprouted?
Who's there?
It's you.
I didn't expect to run into you here.
I was surprised
and exposed my whereabouts.
So you are
the gardener ordered to plant the Qionghua,
Lady Fang.
Interesting.
I didn't expect the Qionghua seeds
to end up in your hands.
Congratulations.
Why are you here?
Qionghua seeds are rare,
and Qionghua is also a rare thing.
I'm just
curious.
You won't expose me, will you?
It took me a lot of effort to sneak in.
If you want to see the Qionghua,
you'll have to wait a few days.
It hasn't bloomed yet.
That's a pity.
In a few days,
I'll be leaving Kuizhou.
Quantan wolf-tooth arrow.
A souvenir.
This injury is old.
The scar is too dark.
Just using lead powder
might not cover it.
Don't move.
In all my years of traveling,
everyone just stares at my goods.
This is the first time
someone has stared at my scar.
Beautiful.
You have such skillful hands.
Your craftsmanship is really good.
What's wrong?
In Kuizhou,
a thin woman can't even be a makeup artist.
This is the first time
someone praised my craftsmanship
instead of Qingcheng's.
In Kuizhou,
life for a thin woman is indeed not easy.
Have you ever thought about
living a different way of life?
A different
way of life?
Yes.
The world is big.
With your excellent makeup skills,
you can make a living anywhere.
Why be trapped in this hellhole?
I have heard that
outside of Kuizhou,
thin girls can write and do accounts,
read and reason,
and even marry freely.
But to get out
is not easy.
As a woman,
getting a travel permit
is as hard as climbing to heaven.
Moreover,
I still have unfinished business here.
I
don't like owing favors the most.
This painting is beautiful.
I like it.
Then I must give you a gift in return.
Tell me what you want.
As long as it exists in this world,
I can get it for you.
As for gold and silver,
I don't need them.
I've been watched closely lately
and can't leave the mansion.
How about you help me put on a play?
A play?
Why is Nanny Chang here again?
She said she's here to check the progress of planting flowers.
Let's go.
Nanny.
Planting this flower this time
took me a lot of effort.
Wait until the day it sprouts,
I will definitely
tell Mother immediately.
You have worked hard, Lady Fang.
I will go and report now.
Nanny.
You have worked hard, Sir.
The sprouting of the viburnum flower is just around the corner.
I will go and report now.
Madam will surely sleep well tonight.
Is this it?
May I ask,
has anyone gone missing in the mansion recently?
My cousin is missing.
Daoist,
can you calculate where she is?
Is your cousin
the master of this mansion?
Yes, she is the Madam.
That's right.
I just arrived in Kuizhou today,
and saw blood and evil spirits soaring into the sky over your mansion.
Your cousin's disappearance
must be related to the strange phenomenon in the mansion.
Could you tell me the Madam's birth dates?
Wait.
Husband,
my cousin has been missing for many days.
What's the harm in letting the Daoist take a look?
Did the Madam get married recently?
Is the other master
of this mansion present?
I am.
Then please, Sir,
tell me your birth dates.
Yes.
What's the harm in calculating?
This is bad.
My cousin...
Something really happened.
The birth dates of the Madam and you
are originally a situation of the Owl God snatching food.
They both have wealthy lives.
If they separate, it's fine.
But if they are together,
there will be a great disaster.
It will even implicate their closest relatives.
Daoist,
is there a way to solve this?
If the Madam and the husband are still entangled,
the husband's relatives
will also suffer a bloody disaster.
Nonsense!
Why are you leaving?
What an attitude.
Daoist,
please save my cousin.
I can't.
Master's complexion is much better recently.
I made this Zichen Liangyi soup
myself.
It is brewed
with pinellia and dwarf lilyturf.
Try it, my Lord. It's good for your health.
Be careful, it's hot.
How thoughtful.
Momo, you were not serving in the courtyard
today.
To report to the Commander,
I just went to the Third Young Master's residence.
Thanks to Madam's grace,
Fang has been tasked with cultivating viburnum.
I went there to check on it.
Fang.
Her again.
You think highly of her.
Such vulgar and lowly people,
I really dislike them.
However,
Those viburnum seeds
were specially found for me by Yi.
I didn't want to break Yi's heart.
Fang volunteered to plant them.
I thought her gardening skills were indeed good,
so I allowed her to do it.
Yes.
I just went to take a look.
Fang has indeed
taken good care of the seeds.
They will sprout
very soon.
It is already a joke for a pariah
to marry into the family as a substitute.
Since it's a joke,
it should end.
Rest assured, my Lord.
I have been thinking about this recently.
However,
Fang Qingcheng's whereabouts are still unknown,
and there are all kinds of rumors out there.
And Fang Zhuozhuo
is Fang Qingcheng's cousin.
If we rashly kick her out now,
I'm afraid the rumors will get worse.
I thought we could delay it for now.
Things will work out eventually.
As for this matter,
you just handle it.
Yes.
Do you have anything else to say?
When I was leaving the Third Young Master's residence,
I met a Taoist priest.
He said in the Master's residence,
there was a bloody aura soaring into the sky.
The priest also
asked for the birth dates of the Third Young Master and Lady Fang.
He said they are
in a situation of evil spirits snatching food.
If the Third Young Master continues to be entangled with the Young Madam,
I'm afraid
it will bring disaster to his closest relatives.
How dare you!
Calm down, my Lord.
Your health is important.
Yes, yes, yes.
The Third Young Master's marriage
to that merchant woman
should be canceled.
You go handle it.
Make it decent.
Yes.
This priest is too ridiculous.
Even if I gave him my birth date,
he could probably make something up.
The engagement absolutely cannot be canceled.
If Qingcheng leaves,
whose life will I use
to exchange for Xin's?
What do you want to do, Young Master?
The origin of this Taoist priest is unknown.
But looking at his eyes,
I feel like I've seen them somewhere before.
Go to the black market.
Yes.
Our Grand Governor
has become increasingly obsessed with divination
since he fell ill.
Qingcheng has no interests involved with him.
As long as Nanny Chang
can convey the Taoist priest's message,
the marriage between Qingcheng and Chu Shengyi
will naturally be dissolved.
Then what about you, Miss?
Qingcheng carries the future of Yanzhi Pavilion on her shoulders.
I must ensure her safe escape first.
As for me,
there are plenty of ways.
But the key to all this is...
The preliminary selection of the Makeup Ceremony is approaching.
There's no time.
The Qionghua flower
must break ground now.